Contact

Visakhapatnam 7338496989 (Mobile) gocharan98@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kilaru-go-charan-9219501a1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

CTF player
Public Speaking
Seminar Presentations

Languages

Hindi (Professional Working)
English (Professional Working)
Telugu (Full Professional)

kilaru Go Charan

CTF player || cybersecurity enthusiast || public speaker Visakhapatnam

Summary

Experienced Member with a demonstrated history of working in the computer and network security industry. Skilled in Hindi, CTF, Presentations, Public Speaking, and English. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from Lovely Professional University.

Experience

CyberHack Member March 2020 - Present (6 months) Punjab, India

Indian Road Safety Campaign
Campus Ambassador
October 2019 - December 2019 (3 months)
Delhi, India

created awareness regarding the Indian road safety.

Cybervie-Ionots Technologies Pvt Ltd Campus Ambassador October 2019 - December 2019 (3 months) Hyderabad, Telangana

conducted awareness programs regarding the courses offered by the company and helped them to increasing their marketing.

Wissenaire, IIT Bhubaneswar Campus Ambassador September 2019 - December 2019 (4 months) Punjab, India

creating awareness regarding the courses offered and events called by them.

Education

Lovely Professional University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2019 - 2023)

Vignan Vidyalayam High School matriculate and senior secondary education, class 6th to 12th · (2014 - 2019)